mercatornet.com 2009-12-19

# MercatorNet: defending human dignity on the internet

## MercatorNet’s Privacy Policy

###### _MercatorNet_ is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide us when using our website. This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit our site. 

#### Information we collect

When you use _MercatorNet_ , you consent to our collection and use of the personal information you provide. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to others without their consent. 

#### How we use information that is collected

We may use personal information in the following ways: 

  * \- To send email acknowledgements of subscription orders or correspondence conducted on the website.
  * \- To send you email renewal notices.
  * \- To enhance existing features or develop new features, products, and services.
  * \- To provide _MercatorNet_ advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our website's user base and usage patterns.
  * \- To process subscriptions, to verify your credit card data, and to send you a receipt.

#### Security

Our website employs security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use a secure server to protect the security of your on-line transactions. 

#### Policy modifications

Our privacy policy may change, so please check back from time to time. 

#### Comments and queries

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, [contact us](http://www.mercatornet.com/info/contact_us/).
